shut that door behind you my name is Joe
Phils the most common question I get
online is how did you get into real
estate and I get it I mean [__] look
at me I I look and talk like a goddamn
complete bunkin and that's because I am
a bunin but I also have a net income of
about $300,000 and passive residual
income off of rental properties I bought
using almost nothing but cash I had in
my own pocket I ran away barefooted and
shirtless from five cop cars in Lincoln
County Georgia when I was 19 years old
and spent 20 months on the lamb when I
was a teenager they caught me 2 days
after my 21st birthday and I did 30
months in the Georgia prison systems in
a 5 foot4 white room I got out of prison
on 8910 August 9th 2010 with nothing but
the clothes on my back the $50 EST State
gives you and the love and support of my
family I had nothing I didn't even have
a [__] driver's license dude I was
living in my mama's basement on Sandy
Run Court wages were low work was slow
and everybody was kind of scrambling
after the 08 recession in the real
estate and construction industry I
didn't have a truck I didn't have
anything but I wanted to start my own
business I've always had an
entrepreneurial Spirit which I believe
is really the main contributing factor
to somebody's success I got my little
business license for Creative
Construction Solutions while I was on
the job site I built all of this from
scratch I made over six figures on the
fourth house I ever fli in my life and I
had made the big times